Anyways back to jokes
[laughs]
a few days ago it happened with me, I was standing at a signal,
Lamborghini car stopped and came beside me,
I got angry, I have reached that age,
I get angry seeing success, it must be happening
with you too,
that time will come soon friends,
you get inspired in your 20s, wow, hardworking man, I earned it with
hard work, I will also get it
in my 30s, it might catch fire, sisterfucker, he must be gambling, he must be
playing betting, I got very angry, I
decided to hit him, I
changed the gear to hit him, okay I did it like this
because I was on the passenger side
[laughs]
[laughs] it
was a cab, not my car, I am not crazy, the
gear changed and I had no control.  The
car jumped and went ahead.  There was an
Alto parked in front, I hit it.   The
Alto driver turned out to be asking for ₹5000.  My
driver got down.  Why won't brother
buy it?
[Praise] The
Alto guy hit me while jumping. We
found all the Alto guys. Do you
know there is an organization of these guys? [Laughter] There is an
Alto WhatsApp group.
150 people came. [Laughter] Brother, everyone hit me a lot.
Women also hit me. There were women
in the group. [Laughter] The women were more dangerous.
An aunty caught me by the collar.
Then he told me many new and unique things about my mother and sister.   She
tells me something herself.  I was also
shocked, what are you talking about?  [laughter]
Not my mom, man.
Tell me, we
live in the same house [laughs].   I
started getting a hint till today.  Then she does everything.
[laughter]
Strange things are going on.  My brother has just got married.
My father called me,
Devesh Bhabhi is coming home.  You will have to make some gesture.
To make her feel welcome.  I will do it.   It
went to his sister-in-law's name.  Got a tattoo on my chest.
Got a negative response.
[laughter] The
parents fainted.
Both together [laughs] Have you
ever seen so much coordination before?  Was
happy for a while.  Truly made for each other.  There should be
more happiness.  After just two minutes,
brother made a good jump.
Whereas he did not even have a wife.  It belonged to the elder one.
[laughter]
This is a different kind of attention.   I started
laughing.  This was dark.
Bored is fine by the way.  [laughter]
[sound of clearing throat] joked on the last show.  The
show is over.  Came out.  A
girl was waiting for me.  By the way,
your brother is saying, are you okay [laughter]
[sound of clearing throat]
[laughter]
no, it's
okay Bhaiya, something very wrong happened with Bhaiya,
Bhaiya could never conceive, it was
stopped in the early stages.
No brother, it is not well.  Sister-in-law is also fine, she is
with me.
Glad
you guys are right.  [laughter]
Listen again.
Sometimes I get a crowd.  [laughs]
I have a friend who has been smoking cigarettes since he was a kid.
Ok?  I have been
drinking two-three packets daily since childhood.
Ok?  I don't smoke cigarettes
since childhood.  [laughter] Okay?  Now look, I'm not
saying my friend should get cancer.   I am
not saying this.  I'm just saying
if he doesn't get cancer.
[laughs]
So I'm screwed, man.
What did I get?   I have been keeping
myself restrained since childhood.  I am
engrossed in penance.  [laughs] I don't feel like
making rings.   Isn't it
?  [laughter] I stopped.  He is
making deceptions in front of me.  He is wooing girls with his style.
I am not doing anything.  Now if
I don't even get to light his funeral pyre.
[laughter]
Now Fuddy's just kind of exploded [laughter].   I am
not saying that you should die today.
I am not an executioner.
Not today.  [nasal voice] Tomorrow or the day after tomorrow,
whenever I take out time,
I don't want to see that day when
my friend and I both turn 90 and are
sitting on a park bench, he takes
out a cigarette box from his pocket [laughs] and
says now you hothead
[laughs]
die before that.  [laughs] He's
my best friend.
He will have to die.
[laughs]
I told my therapist all the jokes.
[laughter] There's ongoing
medication.
Obviously [laughs]
why should I take medicine?  I am a Brahmin.
I asked my therapist.  I
tell jokes.  People also read Hans.  But
I don't connect with the audience.
Strong hearts do not connect.
My name is not screamed at night.  [laughter]
How do I do that?  I have come to watch the show.  Why
will the heart book join?  You all talk nonsense.
[laughter]
All these nonsense things, friend jumped from the roof,
brother got cancer [laughter] I said it is
nonsense, you don't listen,
[laughter] you are
saying that is not the point,
talk in an endearing manner, so much has happened in life, got
married, had a child, no luck,
first of all, no luck, what does it mean, I
give her ₹1000 per month [laughter]
Therapist [sound of clearing throat] what a
cook she is
[laughter] I
give her ₹1000 extra every month, we
talk to her for an hour every Thursday, you guys [
laughter] it is
going well, I can feel the difference
[laughter] I
tried a normal therapist as well and
there was a difference as well,
honestly I have a little anger issue.
So after every session I felt that
my anger was reducing.  But then she would
ask for ₹4000.
[laughter] I'm back there again.
So when I was washing in Poonam's platform.
Then I thought that Devesh would
not be able to bring the wedding procession to this platform now.
[laughter]
That chapter is over.  I think
[laughs]
I was sad for a few days but then I thought it would be okay.
Look, it is written in the scriptures also.
Yes [laughs]
Every child's first love should be his English teacher.
[laughter]
[cheering] [applause] These are the
rules of society.  I didn't make it.
Ok.  [laughter]
I thought, well, she went to Pooram.  I can
refocus.
My English teacher and principal were the same woman.
Her name was Big Ma'am.   It was a
nickname.  There is no Big Ma'am Bhardwaj.
[laughter]
I thought it was time to start courting them.
Ok.  I started working.
Good morning teacher.  Good afternoon teacher.  You
know the drill.
Slowly the magic started working.  One day he
threw his hand on my head like this.  One day he
pulled my cheek.  The fire was burning equally on both sides.
[laughter]
I thought the iron was hot.  I brought the bouquet.
Reached school.   When I went
inside I saw her standing on the stage.   She is
receiving a bouquet from someone else.
[laughter] The
kids around here told me she retired.
Retired
at the age of 17,
anyways Big Maam disappeared [laughs]
her girl joined.  He would have named
us Small Man.
Obviously
I tried to shift to the small man.
But his behavior was not right.
[laughs]
One day she gave me homework to
write 10 sentences about my favourite teacher,
which I thought was a very desperate homework,
you have just come, I
reached home with this poison in my mind, I made Papa do the
homework, I made him do it
because he was also an English teacher
in a government school in
Rajasthan in those days,
English teacher in a government school, means do whatever comes to your mind,
you are an entrepreneur.  [laughter]
Nobody knows what goes on in a startup.  There was a
lot of on-the-job learning.
[laughter] I went to
his school one day.  There was some function.  The
principal made him stand on the stage.
Come back after giving a speech.  The man has literally
said anything.  Cow is your mother.
Real name is Guy.  Hi Koku Hiko Hi Hi
[laughs] I have said whatever
came to my mind, the man is speaking Hindi,
English action, you bloody slaves
under my shoes
[appreciation] the
children are clapping, wow Guruji, wow, you have
torn the clothes [laughs] I have
caught them, make them do their homework,
look my father, he is a teacher by profession, his passion is also
nonsense,
this is always his number one agenda.  [laughter]
He made me write it all down.  Small
Ma'am thinks she is very beautiful.  [laughter]
But she is very next.   She is
desperate.  So and so [laughs] made
me write 10 dirty sentences.  He said yes and went to sleep laughing.   It
works 100 times.  This man does not drink alcohol.
[laughter]
Okay.
I thought he left very happy.  Must have
written something good.  Didn't even share the prank with me.
Left in the dark.
[laughter] The
innocent boy came to get it checked.
Reached school the next day.  She was sitting with a red face.
[laughter] Devesh, come here.  I said
yes, tell me.   Did
you write this?
So this is my copy, right?
[laughter] Read it to me,
Nebo Baby
[laughter].
I said I will read it to you, but I don't know how to read.
I read it and the children are clapping.
What has Devesh written there?
He tore my clothes.   Run away
from here.  Come to school tomorrow only if you
bring your parents with you.  Otherwise there
is no need to come.  I said then I would not like to
come.
Second option clearly better.   By the time I
reached home, my full proof plan was ready.  I
went home and told my mother that I will
not be able to go to school from tomorrow.
Because Small Ma'am has accused me of stealing her purse.
[Laughter]
When this was thought of in my mind, it was played out like this
that I will tell my mother, she will say of
course
then how will you be able to go,
come my dear son, have your food,
I had written these lines [Laughter]
When that woman was told, she did
not know the script at all, she had
left her work and was standing there, don't change.
Going to school.  You are crazy.
You don't know how to solve problems.
[laughter] She
dragged me along.  She is sitting there, she is
sitting here in the small room in front.  I am standing clinging to the wall.
[laughs]
I should get a hole in it, sisterfucker.
[laughter]
[encouraging voice] [applause] I'm standing there with folded
hands.  God, please drop the bus.
Drop the electricity.  Drop it on me.  Finish
everything.
Both the women are speaking.  [laughter] She kept
talking for 15 minutes.  Their words
collide with each other and fall down.  [laughter] They're just out of
earshot.  Breathed after 15 minutes.
He said, hey, we are talking about
different things.
[laughter]
An old man came out from behind the reading, Big
Sir.   The
founder of the school had come from the grave, perhaps I had never
seen him before. He came out and dusted himself off
[laughs] and
said to my mother, look sister [laughs] they will definitely
expel him from the school, if possible
expel him from the house, he is
not fit to be kept [laughs] he is in the second class
dear, he has been expelled, he is sitting in another school.
For admission, my poor mother has to lie
that his father is in the army.
He has been transferred.  [laughter]
He said he was posted 2 kilometres away.
[laughs]
Which BTS army is this in?
[applause] [laughter]